Heezen-Tharp collection: Pacific Ocean
Geography and Map Division, Library of Congress
- Series I: Pacific Ocean
  - Group 17 - Pacific Ocean Province Maps
    - 0019 Statistics of Features 2 to 4 Miles in Length (Folder Barcode: 00275676391)
      a. Positive transparency. b. From 0˚ to 25˚ North and 80˚ to 135˚ West. Chart no.4B South. By Smith, Chase, Farrell, Taylor, and Weed. 1965. Scripps Institution for Bell Telephone Laboratories. Sheet 1 of 3. Primitive province map of the Hawaiian Ridge and the intersection of the Murray and Molokai Fracture Zone.
    - 0020 Preliminary Province Map (Folder Barcode: 00275676391)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 30˚ to 40˚ South and 109˚ to 121˚ East. Color-coded sheet no.410.
    - 0021 West Coast South American Provinces (Folder Barcode: 0027567638A)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 18˚ North to 45˚ South and 67˚ to 90˚ West.
    - 0022 Australian Mid-Ocean Ridge Province Map (Folder Barcode: 0027567638A)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ to 68˚ South and 110˚ to 180˚ West.
    - 0023 Sediment Isopach Map between Australia and Antarctica (Folder Barcode: 0027567638A)
      a. Paper. b. From 30˚ to 67˚ South and 105˚ to 165˚ East. By Houtz and Markel, Figure 3, from seismic profiler studies.
    - 0024 Province Map of Northeastern Pacific (Folder Barcode: 0027567638A)
      a. Positive print. b. From 10˚ to 70˚ North and 70˚ to 150˚ West. Includes earthquake epicenters.
    - 0025 Physiographic Provinces of Australia (Folder Barcode: 0027567638A)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 0˚ to 50˚ South and 110˚ to 180˚ East. Preliminary pen and ink version.
    - 0026 Physiographic Provinces, NP-9 (Folder Barcode: 0027567638A)
      a. Paper. b. From 29˚ to 49˚ North and 115˚ to 150˚ West. Covers standard Navy Ocean-Area, Region-9. Work done by, Lawri. Plate 4.
    - 0027 Province Map of the Pacific Ocean (Folder Barcode: 0027567638A)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 20˚ to 72˚ South and 110˚ East to 150˚ West. Preliminary sketch.
    - 0028 Preliminary Province Map of the Hawaiian Islands (Folder Barcode: 00212680965)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 10˚ to 30˚ North and 140˚ to 180˚ West. Color-coded, rolled item.
    - 0029 Preliminary Province Map of the Hawaiian Islands (Folder Barcode: 00212680965)
  - Group 18 - Pacific Ocean Worksheets
    141 items
    - 0001 [Contour Worksheet] (Folder Barcode: 00275676378)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 10˚ to 30˚ North and 150˚ to 170˚ West.
    - 0002 [Physiographic Diagram of the South China Sea Basin - Western Section] (Folder Barcode: 00275676378)
    - 0003 [Physiographic Sketch in the Vicinity of the Philippine] (Folder Barcode: 00275676378)
      a. Positive print b. From 7˚ North to 16˚ South and 95˚ to 125˚ East.
    - 0004 [Physiographic Sketch in the Vicinity of the Philippine] (Folder Barcode: 00275676378)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 7˚ North to 16˚ South and 95˚ to 125˚ East.
    - 0005 [Physiographic Sketch in the Vicinity of the South China Sea] (Folder Barcode: 00275676378)
      a. Positive print b. From 31˚ North to 8˚ South and 78˚ to 124˚ East.
    - 0006 [Physiographic Sketch in the Vicinity of the South China Sea] (Folder Barcode: 00275676378)
      a. Positive print b. From 25˚ North to 9˚ South and 100˚ to 122˚ East. Page 54.
    - 0007 [Physiographic Sketch in the Vicinity of the South China Sea] (Folder Barcode: 00275676378)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 25˚ North to 9˚ South and 100˚ to 122˚ East. Page 54.
    - 0008 [Pacific Ocean Seamounts] (Folder Barcode: 00275676378)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 8˚ to 10˚ North and 162˚ 50" to 163˚ 50" East. Vema 34.
    - 0009 [Preliminary Worksheet of the Pacific Ocean Showing Upper Jurassic] (Folder Barcode: 00275676378)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 3˚ to 23˚ North and 75˚ to 160˚ West.
    - 0010 [Preliminary Pencil Sketch in the Vicinity of the Northern Mariana Islands] (Folder Barcode: 00275676366)
      a. Tracing paper b. From 0˚ to 35˚ North and 110˚ East to 170˚ West.
    - 0011 [Pacific Ocean Seamounts] (Folder Barcode: 00275676366)
      a. Tracing paper b. From 31˚ to 34˚ North and 153˚ to 161˚ East.
    - 0012 [Color Sketch of Pacific Fracture Zone] (Folder Barcode: 00275676366)
      a. Tracing paper
    - 0013 [Near-final Sketch of the Tonga Trench for the Physiographic (Folder Barcode: 00275676366)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 0˚ to 50˚ South and 140˚ to 150˚ East.
    - 0014 [Physiographic Sketch South of Australia] (Folder Barcode: 00275676366)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 30˚ to 60˚ South and 120˚ to 170˚ East.
    - 0015 [Early Version of Physiographic Province Showing Seamounts, Mid-Oceanic Ridge, and Plate Boundaries] (Folder Barcode: 00275676366)
    - 0016 [Preliminary Sketch of the North Pacific Showing Seamounts and Fault Zones] (Folder Barcode: 00275676354)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 0˚ to 30˚ North and 77˚ to 110˚ West. Sheet 10 of 10.
    - 0017 [Fracture Zone Trends Between New Zealand and Antarctica] (Folder Barcode: 00275676354)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 30˚ to 70˚ South and 120˚ to 180˚ East. Note: "Early conception doodling by Bruce C. Heezen."
    - 0018A [Spot Soundings and Preliminary Provinces of the Peru-Chile Trench] (Folder Barcode: 00275676354)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 8˚ North to 20˚ South and 70˚ to 86˚ West. 1:5,000,000.
    - 0018B [Spot Soundings and Preliminary Provinces of the Peru-Chile Trench] (Folder Barcode: 00275676354)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 20˚ to 46˚ South and 70˚ to 88˚ West. 1:5,000,000.
    - 0018C [Spot Soundings and Preliminary Provinces of the Peru-Chile Trench] (Folder Barcode: 00275676354)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 20˚ to 46˚ South and 20˚ to 90˚ West. 1:5,000,000.
    - 0019 [The Ita Mai Tai Seamount] (Folder Barcode: 00275676342)
      a. Graph paper b. From 12˚ 20" to 13˚ 30" North and 126˚ 35" to 157˚ 13" East. Vema 34, cruise #1. Seamount survey No. 2. 11/12 III 77.
    - 0020A [Tracks East of Japan] (Folder Barcode: 00275676342)
    - 0020B [Contours and Seamounts East of Japan] (Folder Barcode: 00275676342)
    - 0021 [Preliminary Sketch Map of the Tonga Trench] (Folder Barcode: 00275676342)
      a. Tracing paper b. From 30˚ to 41˚ South and 175˚ to 180˚ West. 1:1,000,000.
    - 0022 [Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275676342)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 60˚ to 72˚ South and 160˚ West to 160˚ East.
    - 0023 [Province Map] (Folder Barcode: 00275676342)
    - 0024A [Preliminary Bathymetry of the Pioneer Survey Area North of 45˚ North Latitude] (Folder Barcode: 00275676342)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 44˚ to 54˚ North and 121˚ to 136˚ West.
    - 0024B [Bathymetry of the Pioneer Survey Area North of 45˚ North Latitude] (Folder Barcode: 00275676342)
    - 0025 [Earthquakes and Depths, Color-coded Contours, and Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275676342)
      a. Frosted acetate b. Shows East Pacific Rise, Naska Ridge, etc.
    - 0026 [Color Sketch of the Philippine Sea] (Folder Barcode: 00275676330)
    - 0027 [Tracks and Soundings of U.S. Navy Area 2705S (Folder Barcode: 00275676330)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 27˚ to 34˚ South and 90˚ to 100˚ East.
    - 0028 [Tracks of U.S. Navy Area 2703S] (Folder Barcode: 00275676330)
      a. Paper. b. From 10˚ to 18˚ North and 90˚ to 100˚ East.
    - 0029 [Tracks, Contours and Seamounts] (Folder Barcode: 00275676330)
    - 0030 [Contours of the Southeast Pacific] (Folder Barcode: 00275676329)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 30˚ to 72˚ South and 60˚ to 150˚ West.
    - 0031 [Tracks, Soundings and Profiles Vicinity of the Society Islands] (Folder Barcode: 00275676329)
      a. Frosted acetate b. Notations indicated in red show course changes. Topographic profile drawn at 100:1.
    - 0032 [Physiographic Sketches and Tracks of the North Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275676329)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 30˚ to 60˚ North and 110˚ West to 160˚ East.
    - 0033 [Color-coded Tracks of the Central Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275676329)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 10˚ North to 30˚ South and 70˚ to 150˚ West.
    - 0034 [Preliminary Sketch Map Showing Major Trends, Seamounts, Continental Slope and Abyssal Plain for the North Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275676329)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 30˚ to 60˚ North and 150˚ West to 125˚ East.
    - 0035 [Province Map of the Southwest Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275676317)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 30˚ to 70˚ South and 150˚ West to 110˚ East. Includes detailed province information for Australia and Tasmania.
    - 0036 [Contour Sketch off the Baha Peninsula] (Folder Barcode: 00275676317)
      a. Tracing paper b. From 22˚ to 30˚ North and 108˚ to 120˚ West.
    - 0037 [Sketch of the Aleutian Trench Slope] (Folder Barcode: 00275676317)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 51˚ to 55˚ North and 170˚ to 175˚ East. From the Nichols and Perry maps, 1966, U.S. Geological Survey.
    - 0038 [Contours of the Northern Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275676317)
    - 0039 [Contours of the Southeast Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275676317)
      a. Tracing Paper b. From 30˚ to 72˚ South and 60˚ to 180˚ West.
    - 0040 [Province Map of the South Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275676317)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 49˚ to 72˚ South and 165˚ West to 112˚ East.
    - 0041 [Contours and Tracks - Southwest Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275676305)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 0˚ to 48˚ South and 160˚ West to 110˚ East.
    - 0042 [Colored Province Map on a French Base] (Folder Barcode: 00275676305)
      a. Paper. b. From 10˚ to 48˚ South and 165˚ West to 144˚ East.
    - 0043 [Tracks and Contours of the South Pacific Ocean - in French] (Folder Barcode: 00275676305)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 0˚ to 50˚ South and 160˚ West to 110˚ East.
    - 0044 [Province Map of the Western Pacific Ocean (Folder Barcode: 00275676305)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 45˚ to 70˚ South and 150˚ West to 110˚ East.
    - 0045 [Tracings of Pacific Ocean PDR Records of the Ita Mai Tai Seamounts] (Folder Barcode: 00275676305)
    - 0046 [Preliminary Physiographic Sketch] (Folder Barcode: 00275676299)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 30˚ to 40˚ South and 109˚ to 121˚ East.
    - 0047 [Preliminary Physiographic Sketch] (Folder Barcode: 00275676299)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 30˚ to 42˚ South and 121˚ to 133˚ East.
    - 0048 [Trend Sketch] (Folder Barcode: 00275676299)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 60˚ to 63˚ South and 60˚ to 70˚ West. Note: "True deep trends are covered by mud by RUF but exist."
    - 0049 [Tracks and Soundings Worksheet - Australia and New Zealand] (Folder Barcode: 00275676299)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 30˚ to 70˚ South and 150˚ West to 120˚ East.
    - 0050 [Gridded Worksheet with Tracks and Selected Soundings - West Central Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275676299)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 30˚ North to 30˚ South and 150˚ West to 120˚ East.
    - 0051 [Preliminary Sketch Map of the West Central Pacific Ocean with Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275676287)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 30˚ North to 55˚ South and 80˚ to 155˚ East.
    - 0052 [Sketch of the Aleutian Trench Slope] (Folder Barcode: 00275676287)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 50˚ to 55˚ North and 175˚ to 180˚ East. From the Nichols and Perry maps, 1966, U.S. Geological Survey. Sheet 2 of 6.
    - 0053 [Conceptual Doodling of Pacific Ocean by Bruce C. Heezen] (Folder Barcode: 00275676287)
      a. Frosted acetate b. Rolled item
    - 0054 [Northeast Pacific Ocean Contours and Depths Including the Hawaiian Islands] (Folder Barcode: 00275676287)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 15˚ to 31˚ North and 150˚ to 160˚ West. Rolled item.
    - 0055 [Preliminary Province Map] (Folder Barcode: 00275676287)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 4˚ South to 10˚ North and 140˚ to 150˚ East. Rolled item.
    - 0056 [Fracture Zones in the East Pacific Ocean as well as Regional Gradients] (Folder Barcode: 00275676287)
      a. Frosted acetate b. Rolled item.
    - 0057 [Preliminary Province Map] (Folder Barcode: 00275676287)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 45˚ to 51˚ South and 151˚ to 160˚ West. 1:1,000,000. Rolled item.
    - 0058 [North Pacific Ocean Sketch and Plotting Sheet] (Folder Barcode: 00275676287)
      a. Frosted acetate b. Scaled from contours by Marie Tharp. Note: "Form lines used in (?) and that is where the regional gradient is shown as a sea mount."
    - 0059 [Topographic Worksheet] (Folder Barcode: 00275676287)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 0˚ to 10˚ North and 50˚ to 80˚ West. Minimal color-coded contours and depths.
    - 0060 [Topographic Worksheet] (Folder Barcode: 00275676287)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 40˚ to 50˚ South and 155˚ to 180˚ East. Minimal contours.
    - 0061 [Brain Storm Worksheet] (Folder Barcode: 00275676287)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 20˚ to 23˚ North and 132˚ to 137˚ East. Colored contours.
    - 0062 Eltanin 24 and 28 Intermediate Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676287)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 30˚ to 72˚ South and 60˚ to 150˚ West. Tracks with soundings and structure. Scale: 1:10,000,000.
    - 0063 Geologic Sketch Map (Folder Barcode: 00275676275)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 50˚ to 55˚ North and 175˚ to 180˚ West.
    - 0064 Preliminary Province Map of the Eastern Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676275)
      a. Linen. b. From 50˚ South to 60˚ North and 70˚ to 140˚ West.
    - 0065 Contour Sketch map (Folder Barcode: 00275676275)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 17˚ to 23˚ North and 110˚ to 116˚ West.
    - 0066 Contour Sketch map (Folder Barcode: 00275676275)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 23˚ to 28˚ North and 111˚ to 120˚ West.
    - 0067 Contour Sketch map (Folder Barcode: 00275676275)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 14˚ to 23˚ North and 93˚ to 106˚ West.
    - 0068 Contour Sketch map (Folder Barcode: 00275676263)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 14˚ to 23˚ North and 92˚ to 120˚ West.
    - 0069 Contour Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676263)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 18˚ to 32˚ North and 105˚ to 125˚ West.
    - 0070A Tasman Sea (Folder Barcode: 00275676263)
      a. Positive transparency. b. Base grid, sheet no.3. Used for Atlas Geologique.
    - 0070B Tasman Sea (Folder Barcode: 00275676263)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. 1˚ grid, sheet 4.
    - 0070C Tasman Sea (Folder Barcode: 00275676263)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 5˚ to 45˚ South and 145˚ East to 170˚ West.
    - 0070D Tasman Sea (Folder Barcode: 00275676263)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. Contour overlay. Atlas Geologique -16
    - 0070E Tasman Sea (Folder Barcode: 00275676263)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. Bathymetry overlay in the vicinity of Australia and New Zealand.
    - 0071 Pacific Contours (Folder Barcode: 00275676251)
      a. Tracing paper. b. 6˚ 30’ by 85˚ (no other information).
    - 0072 Contour Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676251)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 3˚ 30’ to 4˚ 20’ North and 80˚ 50’ to 82˚ 10’ West.
    - 0073 Contour Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676251)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 40˚ to 60˚ North and 140˚ to 170˚ West. Overlay to “Bathymetry of the North Central Pacific.”
    - 0074 North Central Pacific Bathymetry Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676251)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 40˚ to 60˚ North and 140˚ to 170˚ West. Overlay to a transparency of “Bathymetry of the North Central Pacific.” Sheet 2 of 4.
    - 0075 North Central Pacific Bathymetry Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676251)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 140˚ to 170˚ West. Overlay to a transparency of “Bathymetry of the North Central Pacific.” Sheet 4 of 4.
    - 0076 Pacific Seamount Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676251, 0027567624A)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 110˚ to 140˚ West.
    - 0077 Northern Pacific Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 0027567624A)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 150˚ West to 150˚ East. Covers the Northern Pacific.
    - 0078 Province Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 0027567624A)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 0˚ to 30˚ North and 120˚ to 150˚ East.
    - 0079 Province Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 0027567624A)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 30˚ South to 30˚ North and 110˚ to 180˚ East. Done with colored pencils.
    - 0080 Track Overlay from Tokyo to the Hawaiian Ridge (Folder Barcode: 0027567624A)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 35˚ to 45˚ North and 140˚ East to 150˚ West.
    - 0081 Age of Pedestals Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 0027567624A)
    - 0082 Select Soundings Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 0027567624A)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 35˚ to 45˚ North and 140˚ East to 150˚ West.
    - 0083 Sheet number2 Worksheet (1406 N) (Folder Barcode: 00275676238)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 31˚ to 35˚ North and 130˚ East to 134˚ West.
    - 0084 Contour Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676238)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 29˚ to 34˚ North and 115˚ East to 120˚ West.
    - 0085 Contour Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676238)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 23˚ to 28˚ North and 112˚ to 120˚ West.
    - 0086 Contour Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676238)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 17˚ to 23˚ North and 101˚ to 110˚ West.
    - 0087 Contour Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676238)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 14˚ to 18˚ North and 100˚ to 109˚ West.
    - 0088 Isopocus Map Showing Material Removed between Augues 1934 and September 1935 (Folder Barcode: 00275676238)
      a. Frosted acetate.
    - 0089 Contour Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676238)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. Covers 1003 N.
    - 0090 Seamount Overlay for the Panama Basin (Folder Barcode: 00275676226)
      a. Frosted acetate overlay on paper. b. From 4˚ South to 10˚ North and 77˚ to 93˚ West.
    - 0091 Contour Worksheet near North Island New Zealand (Folder Barcode: 00275676226)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 37˚ to 43˚ South and 174˚ East to 179˚ West.
    - 0092 Tonga Trench Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676226)
      a. Paper. b. From 37˚ to 41˚ South and 150˚ West to 170˚ East. Shows a zig-zag route across the trench.
    - 0093 Province Worksheet South of Australia (Folder Barcode: 00275676226)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 30˚ to 67˚ South and 110˚ West to 180˚ East.
    - 0094 Contour Worksheet for the area of New Zealand (Folder Barcode: 00275676226)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 37˚ to 44˚ South and 174˚ to 180˚ East.
    - 0095 Contour Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676214)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 36˚ to 40˚ North and 56˚ to 66˚ West.
    - 0096 Province Map Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676214)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 38˚ to 44˚ South and 174˚ to 180˚ East.
    - 0097 Unidentified Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676214)
      a. Tracing paper. b. Includes some contours.
    - 0098 Color-coded Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275676214)
    - 0099 Pacific Ocean Fiji Islands (Folder Barcode: 00275676214)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 19˚ to 20˚ North and 170˚ to 180˚ East. Color-coded provinces.
    - 0100 South Pacific Ocean Sketches (Folder Barcode: 00275676214)
      a. Positive transparency. b. From 23˚ to 29˚ North and 160˚ to 170˚ East. Covers areas 2005 N.
    - 0101 Preliminary Province Map (Folder Barcode: 00275676202)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. 44˚ South and 168˚ 30’ East.
    - 0102 South Pacific Ocean Sketches (Folder Barcode: 00275676202)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 30˚ to 40˚ South and 90˚ to 120˚ East.
    - 0103 Pacific Ocean Geisha Guyot (Folder Barcode: 00275676202)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 25˚ to 30˚ North and 140˚ to 150˚ East.
    - 0104 Select Sounding Sheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676202)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 10˚ North to 50˚ South and 70˚ to 84˚ West.
    - 0105 Worksheet for the Samoa Islands (Folder Barcode: 00275676202)
    - 0106 Southwest Pacific: Early Versions of the Diamantina Fracture Zone (Folder Barcode: 00275676202)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 30˚ to 40˚ South and 100˚ to 130˚ East. Obsolete, pre-Eltanan 55.
    - 0107 New Zealand Area Province Map (Folder Barcode: 00275676202)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 30˚ to 50˚ South and 165˚ East to 175˚ West.
    - 0108 New Zealand Area – Preliminary Physiographic Diagram Sketch (Folder Barcode: 00275676202)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. Pencil sketch with selected soundings.
    - 0109 Southeast Pacific Fracture Zones (Folder Barcode: 00275676202)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 35˚ to 72˚ South and 150˚ West to 160˚ East.
    - 0110 Soundings and Contours (Folder Barcode: 00275676202)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 27˚ to 38˚ South and 175˚ West to 180˚ West.
    - 0111 Soundings and Province Map (Folder Barcode: 00275676202)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 28˚ to 32˚ South and 110˚ to 120˚ East. Covers 2505 and 2506 S.
    - 0112 Spot Soundings off the North American Coast (Folder Barcode: 00275676196)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 20˚ to 50˚ South and 70˚ West to 84˚ West.
    - 0113 Soundings on the Peru-Chile Trench (Folder Barcode: 00275676196)
      a. Positive print. b. From 24˚ to 47˚ South and 70˚ to 90˚ West. Includes some color province map data.
    - 0114 Sketch Map with Overlay of the Western Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676196)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 15˚ to 36˚ South and 113˚ to 125˚ East. “From tectonics of Australia per Allen Lowery, Geologic Society of Australia, 1960”
    - 0115 Pacific Geology (Folder Barcode: 00275676196)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. Covers the entire Pacific Ocean.
    - 0116 Province Data (Folder Barcode: 00275676196)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 60˚ North to 10˚ South and 90˚ West to 130˚ East.
    - 0117 Pacific Ocean Earthquakes (Folder Barcode: 00275676196)
      a. Paper. b. Covers the entire Pacific region. Final first proof, but only shows epicenters for on land.
    - 0118 Master Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676196)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. Covers BC1805 S, from 17˚ to 30˚ South and 170˚ East to 180˚ West. Complex map, including tracks, soundings, geology, and province information. Includes numerous inserts and colored pencil information.
    - 0119 Master Worksheet (Folder Barcode: 00275676196)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ to 44˚ South and 178˚ East to 176˚ West. Complex map including tracks, soundings, geology, and province information. Includes numerous inserts and colored pencil information.
    - 0120 Preliminary Physiographic Diagram data for the Northern Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676184)
      a. Paper. b. From 30˚ to 70˚ North and 120˚ East to 120˚ West.
    - 0121 Early Physiographic Diagram of the Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676184)
      a. Paper. b. From 20˚ to 70˚ North and 60˚ West to 90˚ East. Pencil sketch on the final first proof print of the Pacific Ocean.
    - 0122 Bathymetry of the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676184)
      a. Paper. b. From 6˚ to 37˚ South and 140˚ East to 170˚ West.
    - 0123 Tracing Australian Continental Shelf (1) (Folder Barcode: 00275676184)
    - 0124 Tracing Australian Continental Shelf (2) (Folder Barcode: 00275676184)
    - 0125 Tracing Australian Continental Shelf (3) (Folder Barcode: 00275676184)
    - 0126 Tracks and Soundings for the Pacific Southeast (Folder Barcode: 00275676184)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 30˚ to 72˚ South and 20˚ to 110˚ East.
    - 0127 Tracks and Soundings for the West-Central Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676184)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 30˚ to 30˚ South and 120˚ East to 150˚ West.
    - 0128 Sketch Map and Grid of the Eastern Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676184)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 30˚ North to 30˚ South and 60˚ to 150˚ West.
    - 0129 Pacific Tracks and Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275676172)
    - 0130 Geology Worksheet –SE Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676172)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. Covers area North of Australia. Inked version.
    - 0131 Tracings of Profiler Records off Hawaii – Showing Peak to Peak Correlation. (Folder Barcode: 00275676172)